http://www.grandprix.com/privacy

Inside F1, Inc., the developer of the GRANDPRIX.COM
website, recognize that many Internet users are concerned about privacy. Accordingly,
we have
developed this notice to explain our online information practices, identify
the kinds of information we collect, and describe how we may use this information.
I. Gathering and Use of Information
Inside F1, Inc. collects only the following information from its users:
anonymous
use
information,
and personally identifiable information.
Anonymous use information may be automatically collected by some of our websites and services as you and others browse the web pages or utilize the services. Such information may include the identity of your internet service provider and its approximate geographic location, the operating system of your computer, the type of web browser you are using, the identity of the website that referred you to our website or services, the time and date that you access the website or services, and the webpages or content that you view. This information may be aggregated and utilized to analyze web traffic and usage or to improve the design and content of our websites and services.
Personally identifiable information, by contrast, is only collected by Inside F1, Inc.
if
you
voluntarily submit them to us, for example, make a purchase from the website.
At present, such information includes your contact information, financial information,
username and password, zip code, gender, and age. We use this information to
contact you, execute orders, collect payments, to respond to your requests and
inquiries concerning our products and services, to notify you of updates and
news, to personalize your browsing experience and to generate anonymous aggregated
demographic information. In addition, we encourage, but do not require, you to
provide us with information about your interests and hobbies so that we can forward
messages and materials to you that we believe you will enjoy.
II. Cookies
Inside F1, Inc.’s websites and services may utilize a standard Internet technology known as cookies, which are small data files that your browser stores on your computer to record your preferences and to remember the information you have accessed or provided in the past. Cookies do not contain personal information about you unless you have voluntarily provided it to us as described above. Most web browsers allow you to disable cookies if you do not wish to receive them.
III. Security Measures
Inside F1, Inc. utilizes reasonable and appropriate measures to safeguard any personal
information that you provide to us. However, since no transmission or storage
of electronic data is ever completely secure, we cannot warrant or guarantee
that your information will never be released in a manner that is inconsistent
with this policy.
IV. Disclosure of Information to Third Parties
Inside F1, Inc. does not disclose any user information other than in the following ways:
Inside F1, Inc. provides statistics related to website traffic, aggregated customer demographics,
and related information to third parties, such as advertisers. This information
is not traceable to individual users of our service.
Inside F1, Inc. may share personally identifiable information with our partners, agents
and contractors in connection with the provision of specific services to users.
We require that these parties not use any such information for any purpose other
that the provision of these services, and require them to comply with our privacy
and security practices.
Inside F1, Inc. reserves the right to disclose any user information when we believe that
doing so is required by law or necessary to protect the property, rights, or
safety of ourselves, visitors to our websites, or other persons, or in the context
of a corporate transaction, such as a divestiture, merger, consolidation, or
asset sale, where there is a pledge of confidentiality from the receiving party.
V. Privacy of Children Under the Age of Thirteen
Inside F1, Inc. is committed to protecting the safety and privacy of children. Inside F1, Inc. does not permit the registration or purchasing of materials from the
website by children known to be under the age of 13. Inside F1, Inc. may collect online
contact
information from a child only for the purpose of responding directly on a one-time
basis to a specific request from the child, or where otherwise permitted by law.
In such case, Inside F1, Inc. will not use the collected information for any other
purpose.
VI. Privacy Policy of Third Party Websites and Content Providers
Some webpages and services may contain content provided by and links to websites
operated by third parties. This Privacy Policy does not extend to such third
party content or websites, and Inside F1, Inc. makes no warranty or representation
concerning the privacy practices of such third parties.
VII. Updates to the Privacy Policy
We may modify this Privacy Policy at any time, and such modification shall be
effective immediately upon posting on this webpage. Such posting will constitute
notice to you of the revised policy. Therefore, you agree to review this page
periodically, and your continued access or use of the Inside F1, Inc.
website or services shall be deemed your acceptance of any modifications.
VIII. Contact Information
If you have any questions, concerns, or comments regarding this Privacy Policy, please do not hesitate to contact us at:
Privacy Coordinator
Inside F1, Inc.
PO Box 4
Palisades, NY 10964
